const contest_40_2 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "If $a=(x+1) /(2 x-1)$, express $(2 a+1) /(a-1)$ in terms of $x$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$(4 x+1) /(2-x)$\n$[(2(x+1)+(2 x-1)) /((x+1)-(2 x-1))=(4 x+1) /(2-x)]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Opponent_Answer": 3,
        "Opponent_Time": 24,
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Algebraic Manipulation", "Rational Expressions"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find a relation between $x$ and $y$ given that $2 \\log x-3 \\log y=1$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$x^{2} / y^{3}=10$, or $x^{2}=10 y^{3}$, or $y^{3}=x^{2} / 10$\n$\\left[\\log \\left(x^{2} / y^{3}\\right)=\\log 10, x^{2} / y^{3}=10\\right.$, or $x^{2}=10 y^{3}$ or $\\left.y^{3}=x^{2} / 10\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Opponent_Answer": 3,
        "Opponent_Time": 30,
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Logarithmic Equations", "Algebra"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the domain of the function $y=\\sqrt{ }(3-x)$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\{x: x \\leq 3\\}$\n[function defined for $(3-x) \\geq 0,3 \\geq x$, or $x \\leq 3$ ]",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Function Domains", "Square Roots"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Why is it that jams and dried meats often do not require refrigeration to prevent spoilage?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Enzymes and microorganisms that cause spoilage work best in wet conditions. Dried food is thus better preserved. / The sugar in jam reduces hydration by thickening. The thicker the jam, the longer it takes to spoil, the juicier the jam, the sooner it will spoil. / low water activity",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Food Preservation", "Enzymes and Microorganisms"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Population growth is always finite or determinate. Under what circumstances is population growth maximal?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Population growth could be infinite when there are unlimited resources, such as space food and shelter, and where there are no deaths due to natural disasters.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Population Growth", "Ecology"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Why is it important for the mammalian lung never to become completely empty?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "If this residual volume did not exist and the lungs emptied completely, the lung tissues would stick together and the energy necessary to re-inflate the lung could be too great to overcome. Therefore, there is always some air remaining in the lungs.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Respiratory System", "Lung Function"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Give the ice point on the thermodynamic scale.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$273.15 \\mathrm{~K}$",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Thermodynamic Scale", "Temperature"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Why is a steam burn more painful than a burn from boiling water at the same temperature?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Condensation of the steam injects additional energy into the burn",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Heat Transfer", "Thermal Injuries"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Why does a bird perching on a live uninsulated high-tension cable not get electrocuted?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Insufficient potential difference across the feet of the bird to cause significant current flow through the bird",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 30,
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Electricity", "Electrocution"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Give the two main sources that contribute to background radiation we all receive or are exposed to in our environment on earth.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "i) Cosmic rays;\nii) Natural radioactivity of certain radioisotopes in the soil. e.g. $\\mathrm{K}-40$, Radium, Radon.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Radiation", "Background Radiation"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Between the molecules of aspirin and paracetamol, two common analgesics the following functional groups can be identified. Indicate which drug has which functional group(s):\ni) Ester ii) Amide iii) Phenol iv) Carboxylic acid.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Aspirin: Ester and Carboxylic acid $\\quad\\left[o-\\mathrm{HOOC}-\\mathrm{C}_{6} \\mathrm{H}_{4}^{-}\\right.$\n$\\left.\\mathrm{OCOCH}_{3}\\right]$\nParacetamol:\n$\\left.\\mathrm{HO}-\\mathrm{C}_{6} \\mathrm{H}_{4}-\\mathrm{NHCOCH}_{3}\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Organic Chemistry", "Functional Groups"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A flask contains $0.200 \\mathrm{~mol}$ of nitrogen gas, $0.100 \\mathrm{~mol}$ of oxygen gas and $0.300 \\mathrm{~mol}$ of argon gas at a total pressure of $240 \\mathrm{kPa}$. How many moles of oxygen gas must be added to the flask to raise the total pressure to $300 \\mathrm{kPa}$ ?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "0.150 mol",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Opponent_Answer": 0,
        "Opponent_Time": 0,
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Gas Laws", "Partial Pressures"]
    }
]

export default contest_40_2